[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What version of Monopoly was produced in 1978 by retailer Neiman Marcus?", "correct_answer": "Chocolate Monopoly", "incorrect_answers": ["Deluxe Edition Monopoly", "Golden Monopoly", "Glass Monopoly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what 1997 movie does the following exchange take place?\nMelvin Udall: You make me want to be a better man. \nCarol Connelly: ...Thats maybe the best compliment of my life.", "correct_answer": "As Good as It Gets", "incorrect_answers": ["A Few Good Men", "Scent of a Woman", "Somethings Gotta Give"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the breed of animal created from the crossing of a male lion and a female tiger?", "correct_answer": "Liger", "incorrect_answers": ["Tigon", "Tiges", "Ligon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do adult jellyfish reproduce asexually?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Narcissistic is a word that applies to someone who has a pervasive pattern of cruel, demeaning, and aggressive behavior, beginning in early adulthood.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1658 he became the first person to describe and observe red blood cells (erythrocytes).", "correct_answer": "Jan Swammerdan", "incorrect_answers": ["William Osler", "Marcello Malpighi", "Felix Bernstein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country are Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid trying to get to throughout the self-titled movie?", "correct_answer": "Bolivia", "incorrect_answers": ["Mexico", "Australia", "Brazil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The USA has an extensive Interstate Highway System. What five state capitals are NOT directly served by this system?", "correct_answer": "Juneau, Dover, Jefferson City, Pierre, Carson City", "incorrect_answers": ["Juneau, Dover, Carson City, Honolulu, Pierre", "Juneau, Honolulu, Jefferson City, Carson City, Pierre", "Juneau, Honolulu, Salem, Columbia,  Salt Lake City"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What to the following files have in common: Twins Effect 2, Cradle 2 the Grave, Yakuza, Romeo Must Die?", "correct_answer": "They were all directed by the same man", "incorrect_answers": ["They were produced by the same company", "All were shot in the same country", "All feature the same actor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what shape is the Japanese cake called Taiyaki traditionally made?", "correct_answer": "Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Baby", "Octopus", "Crescent moon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who invented the water thermometer?", "correct_answer": "Galileo", "incorrect_answers": ["Fahrenheit", "Celsius", "Santorio Santorio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This famous song was written about a love letter to a girl named Wendy. The writer loves her, but just has to get out of town.  What is the name of the song?", "correct_answer": "Born to Run", "incorrect_answers": ["The Letter", "Love on the Rocks", "The Streets of This Town"]}]